University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1966-2018; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.; 505 Digital Files
  - 2016-2017 Academic Year Legislation, 2016 July-2017 June
    - 1617-01 Proposal To Establish A Graduate Certificate Program In International Education Management, 2016 September 19
    - 1617-01 Approval (.docx), 2016 October 4
    - 1617-01 Approval (.pdf), 2016 October 6
    - 1617-02 Proposal To Establish A Master Of Science (M.S.) Program In Geographic Information Science, 2017 February 27
    - 1617-02 Approval, 2017 March 13
    - 1617-03 Proposal To Establish B.A. / M.I.A. Programs, 2017 April 17
    - 1617-03 Approval, 2017 May 9
    - 1617-04 Proposal To Establish An M.S. In Data Science, 2017 April 18
    - 1617-04 Approval, 2017 May 11
    - 1617-05 Proposal To Establish A Graduate Certificate Program In Community College Leadership, 2017 April 18
    - 1617-06 Proposal To Create Minor In Leadership, 2017 May 1
    - 1617-01A Amendment Re: Section Ix Of The Charter, 2017 May 1
    - 1617-02A Amendment Re Updates To Section X.7 (Cpca), 2017 May 1
    - 1617-01BA Amendment For Part Time Representation, 2017 March 21
    - 1617-02BA Amendment Defining Quorum For Senate Meetings, 2017 March 21
  - 2015-2016 Academic Year Legislation, 2015 July-2016 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2015-2016
    - 1516-01R Resolution On Emeriti Participation In The University Senate, 2016 April 18
    - 1516-01 Proposal To Establish A Master Of Science (M.S.) Program In Counseling Psychology, 2015 November 18
    - 1516-01 Approval, 2015 November 18
    - 1516-01 Tracking, 2015 November 18
    - 1516-02 Proposal To Establish A B.A. English/M.A. Liberal Studies Program, 2015 November 9
    - 1516-02 Approval, 2015 December 15
    - 1516-03 Proposal To Establish A Graduate Certificate Program In Tesol Online, 2016 February 29
    - 1516-03 Approval, 2016 March 29
    - 1516-04 Proposal To Establish A Bachelor Of Arts And A Bachelor Of Science In Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security And Cybersecurity, 2016 April 27
    - 1516-04 Approval, 2016 April 27
    - 1516-05 Proposal To Amend Policy Pertaining To Certifiable Full-Time Graduate Enrollment Status, 2016 May 2
    - 1516-05 Approval, 2016 May 11
    - 1516-06 Proposal To Establish A Graduate Certificate Program In Computing Education, 2016 May 11
    - 1516-06 Approval, 2016 May 11
    - 1516-01A Asymmetry in LISC Standing Committees (.docx), 2015 October 13
    - 1516-01A Asymmetry in LISC Standing Committees (.pdf), 2015 October 20
    - 1516-02A Updates to Section X.4 (GAC) (.docx), 2015 October 13
    - 1516-02A Updates to Section X.4 (GAC) (.pdf), 2015 October 20
  - 2014-2015 Academic Year Legislation, 2014 July-2015 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2014-2015
    - 1415-01R Resolution to Support the Administrative Creation of the College of Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security, and Cybersecurity (.docx), 2015 May 6
    - 1415-01R Resolution to Support the Administrative Creation of the College of Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security, and Cybersecurity (.pdf), 2015 May 6
    - 1415-01 Graduate Certificate Program in Adolescent Special Education for Content Teachers, 2015 March 12
    - 1415-01 Approval, 2015 March 12
    - 1415-02 Bachelor of Science In Computer Engineering, 2015 March 12
    - 1415-02 Approvals, 2015 March 12
    - 1415-02 Approvals, 2015 March 10
    - 1415-03 Graduate Certificate Program in Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security and Cyber Security, 2015 March 31
    - 1415-03 Related documentation, 2015 March-2015 May
    - 1415-04 Deactivate PR Studies Major, 2015 October 13
    - 1415-04 Approval, 2015 October 21
    - 1415-05 Discontinue and Deregister Graduate Programs in Geology, 2015 May 1
    - 1415-05 Approval, 2015 May 13
    - 1415-06 Name Change for the College of Computing and Information (.doc), 2015 April 30
    - 1415-06 Name Change for the College of Computing and Information (.pdf), 2015 May 14
    - 1415-06 Approval, 2015 May 6
    - 1415-07 Advanced Graduate Certificate Program in Adolescent Special Education for Childhood Special Educators, 2015 May 6
    - 1415-07 Approval, 2015 May 13
    - 1415-08 Undergraduate Minor in Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security and Cybersecurity, 2015 May 6
    - 1415-08 Approval, 2015 May 13
    - 1415-09 Bachelor of Science in Human Development, 2015 May 6
    - 1415-09 Approval, 2015 May 13
    - 1415-01A Amendment re Committee on Assessment of Governance and Consultation, 2014 September 23
    - 1415-02A Amendment re Voting for Ex Officio Members of University Senate Councils and Committees (.docx), 2015 May 5
    - 1415-02A Amendment re Voting for Ex Officio Members of University Senate Councils and Committees (.pdf), 2015 May 5
    - 1415-02A Draft Senate minutes for pending agenda, 2015 October 20
  - 2013-2014 Academic Year Legislation, 2013 July-2014 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2013-2014
    - 1314-01 Create BS Degree in Informatics, 2013 November 25
    - 1314-01 Related Documents (.zip), 2013 November-2013 December
    - 1314-02 Digital Forensics Major, 2013 December 2
    - 1314-03 Master of International Affairs (M.I.A.) Degree Program, 2014 March 27
    - 1314-03 Related Documents (.zip), 2014 April-2014 April
    - 1314-04 Graduate Certificate Program in International Health and Human Rights, 2014 April 17
    - 1314-04 Related Documents (.zip), 2014 March-2014 May
    - 1314-05 Graduate Certificate in Teaching Composition, 2014 May 9
    - 1314-05 Related Documents (.zip), 2015 May
    - 1314-06 BS in Interdisciplinary Studies with a Faculty-Initiated Interdisciplinary Concentration in Bio-Instrumentation, 2014 May 9
    - 1314-06 Related Documents (.zip), 2015 May
    - 1314-07 Graduate Certificate Program in English Studies, 2014 May 16
    - 1314-07 Approval, 2015 September 17
    - 1314-01A Dissolution of CAFFECoR, 2013 September 10
    - 1314-01A CAFFECoR report complete.pdf, 2013 September 23
    - 1314-02A Composition of CPCA, 2014 March 31
    - 1314-02A Amendment re CPCA Composition, 2013 November 25
    - 1314-02A Amendment re CPCA Composition_Rev, 2014 February 18
    - 1314-03A Charge of CAFFECoR, 2014 March 31
    - 1314-04A Election Function, 2014 May 9
    - 1314 Reading Department Name Change (not a bill), 2013 November 25
  - 2012-2013 Academic Year Legislation, 2012 July-2013 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2012-2013
    - 1213-01R Resolution re Violation of ByLaws Article S2.2.2, 2012 September 17
    - 1213-02R Resolution re Violation of ByLaws Article S2.4.1, 2012 September 17
    - 1213-03R Responsible Use of Technology Policy, 2012 December 17
    - 1213-03R Responsible Use of Technology Policy (Revision), 2012 December 19
    - 1213-01 Dept. Name Change for Art Department, 2012 December 12
    - 1213-02 Proposal to Modify UA Undergrad. GE Writing Requirement, 2012 November 8
    - 1213-03 Proposal to Establish Grad Cert Program in Global Health Studies, 2012 November 27
    - 1213-04 Name Change for Department of Women's Studies, 2013 April 17
    - 1213-05 Proposal to Modify 9293-08 Capping a Restricted Major, 2013 April 29
    - 1213-06 Change Curriculum of Major & Minor in Public Policy & Managmenet, 2013 April 29
    - 1213-07 Standards on Academic Integrity, 2013 August 29
    - 1213-08 Create Minor in Sustainability, 2013 May 6
    - 1213-08 Create Minor in Sustainability 5-15-13 edit, 2013 May 16
    - 1213-01A Election of Council Chairs, 2012 October 12
    - 1213-01BA Placement of Items on the Senate Agenda--The amendment was put to an electronic vote in the Spring but did not produce the required number of votes to achieve a quorum., 2013 April 12
    - 1213 Report on Res 1112-05R.docx, 2012 November 27
    - 1213 Report on Res 1112-05R.pdf, 2012 November 30
    - 1213 Resolution 5 Committee Report version 2.docx, 2012 October 27
    - 1213 Resolution 5 Committee Report version 2.odt, 2012 October 26
    - 1213 Resolution 5 Committee Report.docx, 2012 October 26
    - 1213 Approvals and other correspondence (.zip), 2012 November-2013 August
  - 2011-2012 Academic Year Legislation, 2011 July-2012 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2011-2012
    - 1112-01R Student Health Insurance Policy, 2011 November 14
    - 1112-02R Evaluation of Shared Services, 2011 December 6
    - 1112-03R Resltn to Investigate Violations of Governance Procedures in Matter of 2010 Program Deactivations, 2012 January 27
    - 1112-04R Resltn to Institute Specific Consultation Procedures before Enaction of Deactivation, 2012 January 27
    - 1112-05R Resltn to Determin offering in European Lang & Classical Studies in Accrdnc w/UA's Mission & Strategic Plan, 2012 January 27
    - 1112-01 Adoption of iClickers for Senate Voting, 2011 September 16
    - 1112-02 Revisions to the Music Minor, 2011 October 6
    - 1112-03 PHI Revisions to Bioethics Minor, 2011 October 31
    - 1112-04 Minor in Informatics, 2011 October 31
    - 1112-05 Degree Requirements for Major in Accounting, 2011 October 31
    - 1112-06 Student Health Insurance Policy (See Resolution 1112-01R), 2011 October 28
    - 1112-07 Documentary Studies Program, 2011 December 6
    - 1112-08 Removal of Principles of a Just Community from UA Documents, 2012 January 9
    - 1112-09 End Admssn to Geology Concentrn of EnvSci BS & Geo Minor in DAES, 2012 February 28
    - 1112-10 Urban Studies & Planning Faculty Interdisciplinary BA, 2012 May 7
    - 1112-11 Revisions to Economics BA, 2012 March 7
    - 1112-12 EAS 2011 Curriculum Revisions, 2012 May 15
    - 1112-13 POS Concentrations, 2012 March 7
    - 1112-14 Prefix Change to PAP Courses, 2012 March 7
    - 1112-15 Revisions to General Education Program, 2012 March 26
    - 1112-16 Proposed Curriculum Revsns in Atmospheric Sci BS & Envrnmntl Sci BS (See 1112-31), 2012 March 12
    - 1112-17 Revisions to INF Major, 2012 May 15
    - 1112-18 Revisions to Policy on Double Majoring, 2012 April 27
    - 1112-19 Revisions to Biology BS Program, 2012 May 15
    - 1112-20 Policy Chng in Internships (UNI390) & Concentrtn of Creation of SO Level Internship (UNI290), 2012 March 26
    - 1112-21 Curriculum Changes in Dept of Music, 2012 May 15
    - 1112-22 Policy & Procedures on Misconduct in Rsrch and Scholarship, 2012 March 28
    - 1112-22 Research Misconduct PolicyBill.docx, 2012 June 27
    - 1112-22_Research_Misconduct_PolicyBillwobillx.pdf, 2012 September 4
    - 1112-23 Degree Requirements for Major in Accounting, 2012 March 26
    - 1112-24 Proposed Creation of Globalization Studies Minor, 2012 April 27
    - 1112-31 Changes to Atmoshperic Sciences B.S & Environmental Sciences B.S., 2012 April 27
    - 1112-01A Ending Time of Senate Meetings, 2011 September 2
    - 1112-02A Appointment of a Parliamentarian, 2011 November 14
    - 1112-03A Amendment to Create Council on Administrative Review and Evals (CARE), 2012 January 6
    - 1112 Accounting program changes.doc, 2011 October 31
    - 1112 GP Response to CARE Amendment.pdf, 2012 July 25
    - 1112 Legislation Approval 6-10-12.pdf, 2012 June 15
    - 1112 October legislation.pdf, 2011 November 4
    - 1112 Prefix Change from RPUB to RPAD.doc, 2012 February 27
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bill of 9-26-11.docx, 2011 October 6
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bill passesd 4-2-12.docx, 2012 April 12
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bill passesd 4-30-12.docx, 2012 May 15
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bill passesd 5-14-12.docx, 2012 May 23
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bills passed 3-5-12.docx, 2012 March 8
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bills passed on 02-06-12.docx, 2012 February 27
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bills passed on 10-24-11.docx, 2011 October 31
    - 1112 Request to Consider Senate Bills passed on 11-21-11.docx, 2011 December 6
    - 1112 RPUB to PRAD program proposal apprvd with comments in commttee.doc, 2012 February 27
  - 2010-2011 Academic Year Legislation, 2010 July-2011 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2010-2011
    - 1011 RES-01 Resolution Concerning Deactivation of Academic Programs, 2010 November 18
    - 1011 RES-02 SUNY Resolution Concerninig Suspension of Programs at UAlbany, 2010 November 19
    - 1011 RES-03 SUNY Resolution Concerning Consultation with Governance, 2010 November 19
    - 1011 RES-04 UFS Statemt & Res re: NYS Executive Budget, 2011 April 8
    - 1011 RES-05 Resolution on General Education, 2011 May 26
    - 1011-01 Chemistry Honors/Creation of Comprehensive Forensic Emphasis, 2010 October 15
    - 1011-01A Amendment re: CPCA Chair defeated 2/14, 2010 October 25
    - 1011-02 Revision to Policy on Student Absences, 2011 July 22
    - 1011-02A Amendment re: Senate Approval of Council Chairs (tabled by GOV), 2010 October 25
    - 1011-03 Proposal to Establish a BS/MA Program in Economics, 2011 July 22
    - 1011-04 Interim General Education Program defeated 2/14/11, 2011 February 3
    - 1011-05 Suspend Admissions to Major & Honors Program in Judaic Studies, 2011 January 24
    - 1011-06 Graduate Certificate in Information Security, 2011 March 22
    - 1011-06 Graduate Certificate in Information Security, 2011 March 3
    - 1011-07 Policies & Procedures on Misconduct in Research & Scholarship, 2011 October 31
    - 1011-08 Revisions to the Major in Journalsim, 2011 March 11
    - 1011-09 Undergraduate Concentration in Entrepreneurship, 2011 March 8
    - 1011-10 Revisions to Political Science/Public Admin. & Policy Internship, 2011 March 24
    - 1011-11 Revisions to Social Welfare Field Seminar, 2011 April 5
    - 1011-12 Certificat of Grad Studies Online Learning & Teaching (COLT), 2011 April 8
    - 1011-13 Admend Policies for submitting Thesis for Masters Degree Rqrmts., 2011 April 8
    - 1011-14 Revision of Documentary Study Program, 2011 April 29
    - 1011-15 Realignment of FMR GPA Requirements w/Schl of Business GPA, 2011 May 5
    - 1011-16 Changes to History Major, 2011 May 18
    - 1011-17 Suspension of Grad Admission to MS Program in Health Policy Mgmt., 2011 May 13
    - 1011 Pres Apprvl of Lgsltn 12-16.pdf, 2010 December 17
    - 1011 Pres Apprvl of Lgsltn 3-21.pdf, 2011 March 22
    - 1011 Pres Apprvl of Lgsltn 4-5.pdf, 2011 April 6
    - 1011 Pres Appvl of Lgsltn Apr-May.pdf, 2011 June 2
    - 1011 Procedures for Legislation Approvals.doc, 2010 June 14
    - 1011 Reqst to Apprv April Legsltn.doc, 2011 April 20
    - 1011 Reqst to Apprv Feb Legsltn.doc, 2011 March 11
    - 1011 Reqst to Apprv March Legsltn.doc, 2011 March 24
    - 1011 Reqst to Apprv May Legsltn.doc, 2011 May 18
    - 1011 Reqst to Apprv Oct Lgsltn.doc, 2011 March 24
    - 1011 Revised CERS Policy -3-3-2011.docx, 2011 April 5
  - 2009-2010 Academic Year Legislation, 2009 July-2010 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2009-2010
    - 0910 RES-01 Establishing a Gen Ed Task Force, 2010 February 9
    - 0910 RES-02 Faculty Evaluation of Administrators (No Senate vote on 3/8, lack of quorom), 2010 April 13
    - 0910 RES-03 PHEEIA Resolution, 2010 June 8
    - 0910-01 Maximum Credit Load, 2010 March 1
    - 0910-02 Graduate Cert. Program in Professional Science Management, 2009 December 14
    - 0910-02 Bill 0910-02 Larry's edits.doc, 2010 January 28
    - 0910-03 Satisfying the Foreign Language Gen Ed with Credits Earned While Studying Abroad, 2010 March 1
    - 0910-04 Honors College Retention Standards--Senate retd to Council, 12/14/09, 2010 April 1
    - 0910-06 Rev. to Honors Program in French Studies, 2010 March 1
    - 0910-07 Revised Absence Policy, 2010 June 8
    - 0910-07 Revised absence policy (with Changes made from the Senate Floor) (2).doc, 2010 June 8
    - 0910-08 Suspend Admissions to Grad Programs in Russian and Russian Translation, 2010 April 9
    - 0910-09 Revision to Policies on Requirement of Minors for Degree Completion, 2010 June 11
    - 0910-10 Policy for Student-elected S/U Grading (Senate retd to UAC, 4/12/10), 2010 April 23
    - 0910-11 Deletion of PJC from UAlbany Documents, 2010 April 8
    - 0910-12 Policy on Misconduct in Research & Scholarship, 2010 June 14
    - 0910-13 Combined Proposals in Globalization Studies, 2010 May 20
    - 0910-14 Organizational Studies, 2010 June 18
    - 0910-15 Suspend Admissions to E&A Science BA, 2010 June 11
    - 0910-16 CHEM Deactivate Major Track BS, 2010 June 11
    - 0910-17 Suspend Minor in Public Health, 2010 June 11
    - 0910-18 CHEM Deactivate 3-2 Program, 2010 May 7
    - 0910 08-27-09 Pres Memo re Legislation.pdf, 2012 October 2
    - 0910 Presidents Memo.pdf, 2010 August 18
  - 2008-2009 Academic Year Legislation, 2008 July-2009 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2008-2009
    - 0809 RES-01 Effect of NYS Budget on SUNY, 2010 June 14
    - 0809 RES-02 Implementing Recommendations of NYS Commission on Higher Education, 2010 June 14
    - 0809 RES-03 SUNY Board of Trustees Resolution Concerning CNSE, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-01 Syllabus Requirement, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-02 Retroactive Inclusion on Dean's List & Commendations for PT Students, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-03 Grade Changes Affecting Honors, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-04 S/U Selection Deadline, 2009 June 18
    - 0809-05 Department Name Change--DAES, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-06 Health Disparities Certificate, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-07 Chemistry Major Forensic Emphasis, 2009 January 7
    - 0809-08 Charter Amendment re: Eligibility to Chair Councils & Committees, 2010 February 22
    - 0809-09 Charter Amendment: Clarifying Amendment on Graduate Courses, 2010 June 15
    - 0809-10 Second Bachelor's Degree, 2009 June 30
    - 0809-11 Bachelor's/Master's Policy Change, 2009 June 30
    - 0809-12 Discontinue Certificate Program in Urban Education, 2009 June 18
    - 0809-13 Senate Charter Amendment to Ensure Better Consultation, 2010 June 15
    - 0809-14 Criminal Justice Program for Honors in the Major, 2009 April 3
    - 0809-15 IRCUAP, 2010 June 15
    - 0809-16 Creation of Task Force for a Smoke-free Campus, 2009 April 6
    - 0809-17 Proposal to Suspend Admission to MAPAP, 2009 April 8
    - 0809-18 GPA Requirement for Admission to School of Education Minor, 2009 June 16
    - 0809-19 International Baccalaureate, 2009 May 1
    - 0809-20 Minor in Neuroscience, 2009 June 16
    - 0809-21 Misconduct Policy, 2009 May 1
    - 0809 Approved legislation.doc, 2009 June 8
    - 0809 Forensic Chemistry Memo.doc, 2008 December 24
    - 0809 GMP Response to Smoking Policy.pdf, 2011 October 5
    - 0809 GP Memo 8-27-09 re Legislation.pdf, 2012 December 11
    - 0809 Legislation Apprvl memo.doc, 2009 March 24
    - 0809 misconuct_Policy_05042009.pdf, 2009 May 1
    - 0809 Proposed Charter Amendment from GAC.docx, 2008 November 7
    - 0809 Provost Palm re MA PhD 1 08 09.doc, 2009 July 8
  - 2007-2008 Academic Year Legislation, 2007 July-2008 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 0708 Resolution 1 Environmental Sustainability Planning, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708 Resolution 2 Congratulating Susan Herbst, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708 Resolution 3 Supporting RPI Senate, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708 Resolution 4 (CAFFECoR) Resolution on Academic Integrity (not approved at 12/3 sen.), 2007 November
    - 0708-01 Faculty-Initiated Major in Public Health, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-02 First Year Experience (FYE) Program; UFSP Courses '9/24/07 NOT APPROVED, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-03 Proposed Amendment of Charter Section X.1.4.3.2 - Senate Officer Elections 10/22/07 considered and 11/26/07 APPROVED, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-04 Proposed Name Change for CETL / ITLAL 10/22 considered(held), 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-05 Proposed Guidelines for the UAlbany Selection Committee for DTP and DSP 10/22/07 app.by senate/not president. Revised & app. @ Senate 3/10/08, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-06 Proposal to Amend the M.S. General Educational Studies Program & Establish new Graduate Certificate Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-07 Expansion of the Minor in Informatics, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-08 Proposal to establish a Ph.D. Program in Communication, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-09 Proposal to Suspend Graduate Admissions in Geological Sciences, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-10 Revision of Requirements to Graduate from the Honors College, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0708-11 Faculty-Initiated Interdisciplinary Major and Minor in Financial Market Regulation., 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-12 Proposed Revisions to Information Technology Policy Usage Committee (Charter Amendment) 5/12/2008 sent to GOV Council, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-13 Minor in Lesbian,Gay,Bisexual,Transgender & Queer Studies, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-14 Financial Analyst Honors Proposal, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-15 Summer/Winter Sessions Deregistration, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-16 Combined B.A. in Economics and M.A. in Public Affairs & Policy, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-17 Deactivation of Asian Studies Major and Minor, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-18 Individual Concentration for Combined MBA Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-19 Combined B.S. in Economics and M.A. in Public Affairs & Policy, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-20 UUNI399 University Peer Educators Course, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-21 Revision of Anthropology Minor Requirements, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 0708-22 Revision of Admission and Retention Criteria to the School of Business Major, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 0708-23 Proposal to Establish a Combined M.A. Women's Studies Ph.D Sociology Program, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 0708-24 University Writing Program, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 0708-25 IRCAP Initial Review Committee of Academic Proposals (Charter Amendment) 5/16/2008 - postponed to next year, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 0708-25_IRCAP_Charter_amendment-5-8-08.doc, 2008 December
    - 0708-26 UFSP101 Proposal, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 0708-27 Proposal to Est.UA Programs Leading to the B.S. in Nanoscale Science & B.S. in Nanoscale Engineering, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 0708-28 Revision to the Minor in Computer Science, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708-29 Computer Science Departmental Honors, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708-30 Revision to the Major in Computer Science, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708-31 Honors Program in Theater, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708-32 Revisions to the Human Biology Major, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708-33 Proposal to Est.UA Programs Leading to the B.S. in Nanoscale Science & B.S. in Nanoscale Engin., 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708-33-Announcement Form-CNSE 4-2-08-No Waiver.doc, 2008 May
    - 0708-34 New Chemical Biology Emphasis within the BS in Chemistry Major, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 0708 Legislation - extra photocopies, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 0708 Approved Senate Bill merge memo.doc, 2008 June 17
    - 0708 Approved Senate Bills merge fields.xls, 2008 June 17
    - 0708 CNSE Undergraduate Curricula Proposal 05-05-2008 UAC Approved (2).doc, 2008 May 7
    - 0708 GAC University at Albany Future Faculty Preparation Program (3).doc, 2008 April 23
    - 0708 HumanBioBill.doc, 2008 May 8
    - 0708 IRCAP Charter amendment-April 23 2008.doc, 2008 April 22
    - 0708 IRCAP Charter amendment-rationale-April 2008.doc, 2008 April 22
    - 0708 Letterhead - University Senate.doc, 2008 May 16
    - 0708 Memo to OIC.doc, 2008 May 16
  - 2006-2007 Academic Year Legislation, 2006 July-2007 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 0607 Resolution 01: Recreational Facilities, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)